https://www.casafresnomadera.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At CASA Fresno Madera (CASA), one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by CASA and how we use it.
LOG FILES
CASA follows a standard procedure of using log files. Utilizing Google Analytics and tracking we log visitors when they visit CASA Fresno Madera. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
EMAIL ADDRESSES AND PERSONAL INFORMATION
CASA Fresno Madera does not sell or share personal information that is collected on the site with any third-party entity, this includes email addresses.
PRIVACY POLICIES
Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that CASA Fresno Madera has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
THIRD PARTY PRIVACY POLICIES
CASA Fresno Madera Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam protection. Their privacy policy can be found here : https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
We use Akismet Spam for spam protection. Their privacy policy can be found here : https://automattic.com/privacy/
We use MailChimp to manage our subscriber list. Their privacy policy can be found here : https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/.
We use Zapier to manage our integration data. Their privacy policy can be found here : https://zapier.com/privacy/.
We use Google Drive and Google Sheet to manage our integration data. Their privacy policy can be found here : https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en.
CHILDREN’S INFORMATION
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
CASA Fresno Madera does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in CASA Fresno Madera. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
SECURITY
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or contacting us.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
CONSENT
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
©2019 CASA Fresno/Madera | 2300 Tulare St, #210 | FRESNO, CA 93721 |
PH: 559.244.6485 | FAX: 559.243.0791
All Rights Reserved. Designed by RAD Ideas
